Though my true power
has been unleashed,
you are still able to keep up.
Yeah.
You're pretty strong, too.
Putting City A back together
might be impossible.
Well, right now I should be
focusing on the battle.
She may be rank 2 or whatever,
but I can't leave it to one little girl.
I got my own ways of
fighting enemies in the air.
Like this!
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
This area's got some nice rubble.
Hurry up and get out of my way.
She's using her psychic power?!
I give up!
We're under attack again!
Return fire!
The guns are jacked!
Seriously?! We're dead meat!
This planet's too tough!
Lord Boros!
I wanna go home...
Such incredible power.
Tornado may actually
bring it down on her own.
I have errands to run.
I will head out now.
Things appear to be under control.
Well, do whatever you like.
Some heroes have already left.
Before I go, Genos, do you have a minute?
There's something I wish to tell you.
Drive Knight, Class S, rank 9.
This is a first...
Listen. Metal Knight is your "enemy."
Be careful.
What are you implying?
You will know soon enough.
But for now, stay away from him.
Bastard.
You sure make things interesting.
I'm beginning to taste victory.
The stiffness in my shoulders is gone.
But I suppose I'm a little rusty.
Bastard, you're still—?
Hey. Forget something?
ATOMIC
SLASH
Atomic Slash!
Insolence...
Such complete insolence!
You move your heart-thing around
your body to hide its location.
But your regeneration always
begins with your head
and in the center lies...
...your heart.
After seeing it so much,
even a monkey'd figure it out.
See? Checkmate.
Noooooo!
Silverfang!
All I needed was one more swing.
Keep your hands to yourself,
Silverfang.
Goodness, I really do need
to do more full-body workouts.
We got all the heads.
That means...victory is ours!
Yah, but there's still that
big-ass ship up there.
All right, this is the last of
the reported survivors.
Let's move!
Right.
Mumen!
Quit your staring and come on!
Yeah, okay.
One punch
Three, Two, One, Kill shot
sanjou! Go on! seiseidoudou!!
I'm here! Go on! Fair and square!
dou nattenda?
What's going on?
nanimo kanjinee?
I don't feel anything
mohaya teki inee!
There's no one to oppose me
Justice! shikkou! mondou muyou!
Justice! Enforcement! No point arguing about it!
ore ga tatsu!! aku o tatsu!!
I'll cut it off! Cut off evil!
gasshou!!
Pray, Beg, Worship!
®
Power, get power
adorenarin afuredasu ze!
Adrenaline's overflowin'!
Power, get power
kitaeta waza o buchikamase!
Strike with force with the technique I mastered
µ
Hero
donna ni tsuyoi yatsu mo chippoke na gaki dattanda
Even the strongest
used to be little noobs
Nice moves.
As I thought, you are strong.
Hero
Of all the myriad beings
I have fought, only you...
yowaki onore norikoe tsuyokunaru
They overcome their weaknesses
and become stronger
...survived this long!
Nobody knows who he is
kami yadoru kobushi kakagete
Raising my fists with gods dwelling in them
ore wa tsukisusumu dake sa
I'll just push onward
Now to release the
destructive energy held within me!
Hero
itsuka haiboku ni odei nameru made
until I taste the dirt
of defeat one day
Any normal creature hit by it
would find even their bones vaporized!
tatakau hero
A Fighting Hero
kodoku na hero
A Solitary Hero
I
Behind you!
I wanna be a saikyou hero!
I wanna be a Superhero!
You were a worthy opponent.
But the outcome
of this battle is clear.
My species won
the struggle to survive
amidst the harsh environment
of our home world.
We possess the ultimate
regenerative abilities.
I, in particular,
have self-healing power,
physical prowess and latent energy
beyond your conception.
A deep wound that would
be fatal for you
heals itself on me in mere moments.
By focusing all my energy
on my destroyed arm,
I can explosively speed up
the healing process.
Good as new.
You, on the other hand,
will only get injured more,
all while your stamina
gradually decreases—
Shut up.
Blah, blah, blah. Aren't you done yet?
With this?
No, not yet!
Meteoric Burst!
The energy shunted from my body
transforms into a propelling force,
elevating speed and power
to a level beyond the limitations...
...of living flesh!
Doing this places enormous stress on my body,
similar to anaerobic exercise.
As a result, it shortens my life.
Therefore, it should only be used as a
trump card for settling fights quickly.
It's listing!
You're doing it!
Awesome, Tornado!
Oh.
I made it.
This man...
...makes me want to go all out!
That's the way, Saitama.
You are indeed worth defeating!
Consecutive Normal Punches.
I will defeat you!
All my energy will be released,
blasting you and
this planet to Hell!
Collapsing Star, Roaring Cannon!
In that case,
I'm using my final move too.
Killer Move: Serious Series...
...Serious Punch.
Did I...lose?
You're still conscious?
You really are strong.
The prophecy held true.
The battle was...hard-fought.
Yeah. It sure was.
You lie.
You had strength to spare.
I never stood a chance.
It wasn't even a battle.
So much for prophecies.
You were too strong...
Saitama...
THE STRONGEST HERO
It's crashing?
Is this Master's doing?
We're done!
The power sphere's been broken!
We're going down!
Lord Boros went wild!
Get out, get out!
- Run!
- Stop shoving, stupid!
I wanna go home, Mommy!
It's coming down.
Huh?
Hey, we better get outta here...!
This is bad. Run for the Association HQ.
Iai! Hold on to me!
I'm okay, Master!
Damn. When did Silverfang get so fast?
Now's not the time to be competitive.
Angel Dash!
Hey pansy, don't you run
in front of me! You're too slow!
Angel Dash!
Don't just say it, move!
- We're gonna crash!
It's down.
All right, let's go.
How did City A end up like this?
CLASS A RANK 1
HANDSOME KAMEN AMAI MASK
All of Class S was meeting today...
Care to explain, Metal Bat?
Huh?
Explain it so I can understand.
Handsome Kamen Amai Mask...
Where the hell'd you pop up from?
I was filming a TV drama
in the next town.
There was a roar and tremors,
so I came and
found City A wiped out.
Monsters on a huge-ass ship
attacked us.
They fired artillery at us
and did all this.
But we took care of it.
"Took care of it," you say?
You call this victory?
Such incompetence.
I'm completely appalled
at all of you!
Hey.
You didn't even get here in time,
so don't go acting all big.
It's true I didn't make it in time,
but you all were right here.
You didn't save a single brick!
We were having a meeting inside
the headquarters building.
We went outside as soon as
the enemy attacked,
but the city was already in ruins.
So what?
You think if you tell them that,
the media will just let all this go?
You...
Whose side are you on?
We did our best.
I'm on the side of justice.
Having Class S heroes
this pathetic...
is an embarrassment.
Anybody this useless
should voluntarily retire.
Hey! Don't start talking crap with us!
Who's gonna care about a pop idol with
a face busted all to Hell?!
Do you have any idea
why I don't move up to Class S?
I remain Class A, Rank 1
so I can prevent
weak, good-for-nothing pissants
like you from moving up to Class S.
Metal Knight, you skip the meeting
and only show up now?
This is...
magnificent!
Metal Knight!
What are you doing here?
The battle is already over.
Metal Knight is your "enemy."
Genos, right?
Do not tell me you have come
to recover the spaceship.
Are you here
so you can create more powerful weapons
with the alien technology?
Precisely.
Powerful weapons
are a necessity...
for the sake of peace.
Even with powerful weapons,
in the hands of heroes like this,
they'd be wasted.
You're mine later, pretty boy.
Watch your ass.
Hey!
I found some alien survivors!
I never thought Lord Boros would lose.
Are we going to be killed?
Maybe we can talk
our way out of this.
Aggh, I'm so hungry!
Idiot! Now's not the time for—
Shh! Someone's coming.
Amai Mask! What the—?
They did not deserve to live.
They were evil.
I swiftly implemented justice, that's all.
I'm sure you understand,
Genos...
You've been busy since the exam.
But from what I saw of
the Deep Sea King incident and today,
you've mostly been a disappointment.
Pay no heed.
Do not worry. I am fine.
He reminds me of how
I was before I met Master.
A man on edge...
too eager to eliminate evil.
Just like me,
he must have gone through
something terrible in his past.
Wait!
Where is Master Saitama?
Oh, I'm out!
Hey!
Why would a Class B like you be inside the ship?
Master!
You are safe!
Hey, Genos!
We're done here. Let's go.
Did you defeat their leader?
Yeah, he was really strong.
Maybe the strongest I've faced.
I see.
So without you, Master,
the prophecy...
about the earth's destruction would have come true.
They're ignoring me?
Nah.
Turns out you can't trust
prophecies to begin with.
Hold it right there!
I don't know how you did it,
but you went in the ship on your own?
You're just a Class B.
How dare you butt in like that?
I didn't need you. I could
have handled it on my own.
- Baldy! Octopus! Boiled egg!
Light bulb! Avocado!
- Lame face! Goblin! Bug! Baldy!
G-Genos.
- Ping-pong ball! Rice grain! Beanhead!
Say something.
- Kettle! Baldy! Kneecap!
- Yes, sir.
Listen, spoiled brat.
Shut up and get lost,
or get beat down.
That's it! Yeah!
Unforgiveable. Me, a brat?
I'm older than you!
Genos?!
You're next, Class B!
Cut it out, Tornado.
You're part of the Association—
a hero, right?
Well, whatever.
Why are there so many troublemakers
amongst the elite heroes?
Genos... Your joints are all bent
the wrong way.
Wait, let me fix you up.
Oh sorry, your arm came off!
My back is killing me.
City A was wiped off the map that day.
The arrival of aliens and
City A's annihilation were history-making events,
the top stories for days.
But eventually the coverage died down
and no one mentioned the
city that had disappeared.
Metal Knight salvaged the spaceship.
Soon thereafter, the Hero Association headquarters
was reconstructed all the stronger,
and became an impenetrable fortress of steel.
The infrastructure was rebuilt
with new roads leading out of HQ.
Heroes were able to deploy quickly to every city.
And heroes Class A and
above were given the option
to live at headquarters.
Ashita e no kaze ni notte kanashimi tachi wo dakishimete
Riding a wind heading for tomorrow,
we cling to our many sorrows
Daijoubu sukoshi yasumou soshite mata susumou
It's alright, let's just rest a bit.
Then let's move forward again.
Sekai wa mawari tsudzukete yagate kienu itami wo shiru
The world will keep on spinning, until we eventually
come to know the pain that won't ever fade.
Sore demo ima me wo tojite
Nonetheless, we close our eyes
Omoi de ga hohoemi ni kawaru
And our memories will become smiles
kibou ga sore wo kanaeru
Our hopes allow it to be so
Itsunomanika hi ga kata mukeba nemuri ni tsutsumarete
And when the sun begins to suddenly
wane, we're enveloped by sleep.
Omoi de yo hohoemi ni kaware
Oh memories, turn to smiles!
deaeta yorokobi dake Taisetsu ni shimattara
Once we've carefully stashed away
only the happiness of our meeting,
sayonara sotto te wo furu yo
We'll say, 'Goodbye'... and
wave our hands tenderly in parting.
You can see it clearly!
The entire building has been
ripped out down to the foundations.
The monster appeared in
City Z, but now City Y is in—
PLUTON, KING OF THE UNDERWORLD
THREAT LEVEL: DRAGON
You humans waste your existence in gluttony,
littering the earth with worthless objects.
Now shall you boil and rot
in the depths of the underworld
that spreads below my mighty snout!
Who do we have here?
A great man who is a hero for fun...
and profit.
A great man?
And...his disciple.
Back to one punch again...
GOD DAMN IT!!